ezrez.com 2011-11-09

# ezRez Software, Inc. Privacy Policy

ezRez Software, Inc. Privacy Policy
What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?
This Privacy Policy describes how ezRez Software, Inc. (“ezRez”) collects, uses, transfers and
discloses personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) that we may obtain about
you through our website located at www.ezrez.com (“Website”). This Privacy Policy does not
cover our use of information collected through any other means. By using the Website, you
acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy.
This Privacy Policy does not apply to or govern the practices of third party companies or
websites that use ezRez products or services, that can be accessed through links contained on
the Website, or that ezRez does not own or control. We are not responsible or liable for the
policies and practices followed by third parties. We encourage you to read the privacy
statements of these companies or websites as their privacy statement may differ from ours.
ezRez knows that you care about how your Personal Information is used and shared, and we
take your privacy seriously. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you
should contact ezRez by email at privacy@ezrez.com.
Personally Identifiable Information We Collect
The information ezRez obtains from you is generally necessary or useful for ezRez to provide
the services or information you have requested, and is provided directly by you in response to
our request for the information. In connection with the services ezRez provides, we may ask
you to provide your name, physical address, ZIP code, phone number, e-mail address, and
services received or requested. Your submission of such information online is deemed your
consent to ezRez’ use of the information as contemplated in this Privacy Policy.
Use of Your Personal Information
ezRez uses your Personal Information obtained through the Website to provide the services or
information you have requested, to personalize your experience on the Website, to provide
customer support, to improve the Website, and for other legitimate business purposes. ezRez
does not currently use your Personal Information to conduct direct marketing, but may do so in
the future.
When We Share Personal Information
ezRez does not share, sell, rent or trade your Personal Information with third parties for their
own promotional purposes. ezRez will not share your Personal Information with other organizations
except as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

ezRez occasionally hires other companies to provide services on its behalf, which include or
may include providing customer support, processing transactions, or performing statistical
analysis of the Website or our services. We may provide Personal Information to these third
parties, but we authorize them to use this Personal Information only in connection with the
services they perform on our behalf, and for no other purpose. In addition, such parties are
bound by contract to establish reasonable measures to protect your Personal Information from
unauthorized access, use or disclosure.
ezRez may also access and/or disclose your Personal Information to protect our rights or
property, to enforce our terms of use and legal notices, as required or permitted by law, or at
the request of government regulators or other law enforcement officials and the courts
(including the issuance of a valid subpoena). We shall have no duty to notify you of such
compliance with the law. We may also access and/or disclose your Personal Information in
connection with the sale of all or substantially all of our assets to which the Website relates.
We maintain reasonable technical and organizational measures to protect Personal Information
against accidental or unlawful destruction or accidental loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure
or access. Unfortunately, no information security system can be 100% secure. As a result,
although we strive to protect your Personal Information, we cannot ensure or warrant the
security of the Personal Information against any possible loss or unauthorized access.
The Website and our services are hosted on servers located in the United States. If you are
located in a non-U.S. jurisdiction, please note that your Personal Information will be transferred
to the United States, a jurisdiction that may not provide an equivalent level of data protection
to the laws in your home country.
Other Information We Collect
Some information may automatically be collected as you browse the Website. Our Website
server automatically collects information such as the domain name of the service providing you
with Internet access, the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the
Internet, the average time spent on the Website, pages viewed, information searched for,
access times, and other relevant statistics.
We also use cookies on the Website. A cookie is a small data file that websites commonly write
to a website visitor's hard drive when a site is visited. A cookie file contains information that
can identify a return visitor each time he or she visits the Website. The Website may use
cookies as a way to measure activity and traffic patterns on the Website in order to continually
improve the visitor's experience. A browser can be set to warn the users before accepting
cookies. Users can choose to refuse cookies by turning them off in the browser. Users do not
need to have cookies turned on to visit the Website.

Your Choices
We do not collect personally identifiable information about you on the Website without your
knowledge, and all such information is collected directly from you. You are not required to
provide us with this information, but if you choose not to, you may not be able to participate in
some of the activities or received some of the benefits available on the Website or through our
services.
You may opt-out of receiving direct marketing email or messages from ezRez at any time by
notifying us via email at privacy@ezrez.com. You may also opt-out by responding to the opt-
out option included with any direct marketing email or message that we send.
Access to Your Personal Information
You can access, correct and update your Personal Information by emailing us at
privacy@ezrez.com.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will post a revised link on the
Website that notifies visitors of the change. You should check the Website periodically to see if
any recent changes to this Privacy Policy have been made. You can also tell if this Privacy Policy
has changed recently by reviewing the Effective Date posted at the beginning of this Privacy
Policy.
Safe Harbor
ezRez, abides by the privacy principles of the U.S.-EU and U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Frameworks as
set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of
data from the European Union.
Effective Date: June 1, 2011
Safe Harbor Privacy Policy
ezRez Software, Inc. (“ezRez”) recognizes that the European Union (“EU”) has an “ominbus”
data protection regime established pursuant to the European Data Protection Directive
(95/46/EC) (the “Directive”) and that Switzerland has adopted a data protection law (together,
“Data Privacy Laws”). Among other things, the Data Privacy Laws generally require “adequate
protection” for the transfer of personally identifiable information about individuals located in
the EU and Switzerland to ezRez’s operations in the United States.

ezRez provides a hosted online travel agency software platform which enables its enterprise
business customers to sell airline flights, hotels, car rentals, and other travel products for cash
and loyalty program points (the “ezRez Service”). In the course of providing the ezRez Service,
ezRez processes its enterprise business customers’ data which includes personal information of
individuals located in the EU and Switzerland who shop for and purchase travel products from
ezRez enterprise business customers via the ezRez Service (“European Travelers” and
“European Traveler Data"). ezRez accordingly adheres to the requirements of the U.S./EU and
U.S./Swiss Safe Harbor Privacy Principles published by the U.S. Department of Commerce ("Safe
Harbor") with respect to certain European Traveler Data received in the United States about
European Travelers. ezRez is not responsible for the content of the information it processes,
nor is it responsible for the way its enterprise business customers treat the Personal
Information they collect or control.
Each of our enterprise business customers acts as the data controller for any European Traveler
Data collected in the EU and Switzerland and subsequently transferred to ezRez in the U.S.
ezRez acts as a data processor on behalf of our enterprise business customers with respect to
such European Traveler Data and accordingly only carries out the instructions of such
customers with regard to the collection, processing, and protection of European Traveler Data.
ezRez generally does not collect personal information directly from individuals in the EU. If
ezRez does collect information directly from individuals within the EU via its Website, it will do
so pursuant to its corporate Privacy Policy in accordance with the Safe Harbor.
For more information about Safe Harbor please refer to the U.S. Department of Commerce
website at http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/. European Travelers may first wish to contact
the enterprise business customer with questions regarding European Traveler Data shared with
ezRez, as this may be the most efficient means of addressing such access requests. European
Travelers may email ezRez at privacy@ezrez.com to review the European Traveler Data that
ezRez holds about them. Any European Traveler who cannot resolve his or her issue directly
with the enterprise business customer or ezRez can contact the local data protection authority
for further information and assistance.
If you have any questions about our Safe Harbor participation, please email us at
privacy@ezrez.com.
Effective Date: June 1, 2011
